question_data = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {"type": "boolean",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.",
         "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "In the Monster Hunter Series, it is possible to capture Elder Dragons.",
         "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "The main playable character of the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot; is a monster.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "Faust is a playable character in &quot;Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "In Until Dawn, both characters Sam and Mike cannot be killed under any means until the final "
                     "chapter of the game.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.",
         "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "&quot;Resident Evil 7&quot; is the first first-person Resident Evil game.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]}
